littledayout.com 2017-08-29

# Privacy Policy - Little Day Out

Little Day Out is a digital media publisher, owned by Big Little Company Pte. Ltd., that provides customers with news and resources about places, events and activities for children, posting opinions of children-related matters, engaging in related interactive forums and discussions. We have a legal obligation to comply with the Personal Data Protection Act 2012 (PDPA) in relation to personal data which we hold about you and we take our responsibilities under the PDPA seriously. We recognise the importance of safeguarding the personal data you have provided us and it is our responsibility to properly manage, protect and process your personal data.

Before submitting your personal information to our Website, please read this Privacy Policy carefully to learn about our privacy practices. ** **

**What We Collect From You**

We receive and store the information you enter on our Website or give us in any other way. This includes information that can identify you (“personal information”), including your first and last name, telephone number, postal and e-mail addresses, user name and password. We may also request information about your personal profile. You can choose not to provide information to us, but in general, some information about you is required in order for you to enjoy the benefits of being a registered member. In addition, some information is also required in order for you to ask us a question or initiate other transactions on our Website.

**Cookies and Other Web Technologies**

Cookies are small data text files and can be stored on your computer’s hard drive (if your Web browser permits). Little Day Out may use cookies for the following general purposes:

(a) To help us recognise your browser as a previous visitor and save and remember any preferences that may have been set while your browser was visiting our site. For example, if you register on our site, we may use cookies to remember your registration information, so you do not need to log into our site each time you visit. We also may record your password in a cookie, if you checked the box entitled “Keep me signed in on this computer unless I sign out.”

(b) To help measure and research the effectiveness of website features and offerings, advertisements, and email communications (by determining which e-mails you open and act upon).

Most browsers should allow you to choose to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, or have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable non-essential types of cookies. Please note that if you refuse to accept cookies, you may not be able to access parts of our Website.

**How We Use Your Data**

Little Day Out uses the information we collect about you for the following general purposes: for registration and to manage your account, including to facilitate your access to and use of our site; to communicate with you in general, including to provide information about Little Day Out and invitations from the Little Day Out community; to enable us to publish your reviews, forum posts, and other content to the Little Day Out community; to respond to your questions and comments; to measure interest in and improve our products, services, and Web site; to notify you about special offers and products or services available from us or our partners that may be of interest to you; to otherwise customise your experience with Little Day Out; to solicit information from you, including through surveys; to resolve disputes or troubleshoot problems; to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; to enforce our Terms of Use Agreement; and as otherwise described to you at the point of collection.

**Email Communications**

We want to make it easy for you to take advantage of children-related opportunities on our Website. One way we do this is by sending you email messages that contain information about your apparent children-related interests. We believe these email messages will provide you with useful information about children-related offers. Please note that you will have the opportunity to choose not to receive these email messages in any such email we send.

In addition to these communications, if you have provided an email address, we may use your personal information to send you notifications about special offers or to tell you about opportunities available from our partners. You may opt-out of any or all marketing communications from Little Day Out in any commercial e-mail we send or at any time, as well as access and update your personal information, by visiting www.littledayout.com and logging into your profile.

**User Profile**

If you choose to create a profile on Little Day Out, certain information in your profile will be publicly viewable and identifiable by clicking your screen name. You will have the ability to view your profile as members of the public will see it.

**How We Protect Your Data** ** **

We treat all information about you securely and with care, guided by our policies and practices.

We do not share your personal contact information (such as email addresses) with unaffiliated third parties so they can serve you with advertisements.

We may allow third parties to collect information about your online activities through cookies and other technologies. These third parties include (1) business partners, who collect information when you view or interact with one of their advertisements on our sites, and (2) advertising networks, who collect information about your interests when you view or interact with one of the advertisements they place on many different Web sites on the Internet. The information gathered by these third parties is used to make predictions about your characteristics, interests or preferences and to display advertisements on our sites and across the Internet tailored to your interests.

We do not permit these third parties to collect personal contact information about you (such as email address) on our site, nor do we share with them any personal information about you.

Please note that we do not have access to or control over cookies or other technologies these third parties may use to collect information about your interests, and the information practices of these third parties are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

**With whom we share your information**

We respect the confidentiality of the personal data you have provided to us. In that regard, we will not disclose your personal data to third parties without first obtaining your consent permitting us to do so.

However, please note that we may share your personal data to the following entities without first obtaining your consent in certain situations, including, without limitation, the following:

(a)  _Third-party vendors_  who provide services or functions on our behalf, including business analytics, customer service, marketing, distribution of surveys or sweepstakes programs, and fraud prevention. We may also authorise third-party vendors to collect information on our behalf, including as necessary to operate features of our website or to facilitate the delivery of online advertising tailored to your interests. Third-party vendors have access to and may collect information only as needed to perform their functions and are not permitted to share or use the information for any other purpose.

(b)  _Business partners_  with whom we may offer products or services in conjunction. You can tell when a third party is involved in a product or service you have requested because their name will appear either with ours or separately. If you choose to access these optional services, we may share information about you, including your personal information, with those partners. Please note that we do not control the privacy practices of these third-party business partners.

We also may share your information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.

We also may share you information when we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of Little Day Out, our customers, or others; and in connection with our Agreement and other agreements, or in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

We also may share aggregate or anonymous information with third parties, including advertisers and investors. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors our Web site receives. This information does not contain any personal information and is used to develop content and services we hope you will find of interest.

The instances listed above are not intended to be exhaustive. For more information on the exceptions, you are encouraged to peruse the Second, Third and Fourth Schedules of the PDPA which is publicly available at [http://statutes.agc.gov.sg](http://statutes.agc.gov.sg/).

Where we disclose your personal data to third parties without your consent, we will employ our best efforts to require such third parties to protect your personal data.

**Request for Access and How You Can Modify Your Data**

You may request to access a copy of the data which we hold about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. We will need enough information from you in order to ascertain your identity as well as the nature of your request, so as to be able to deal with your request. Please notify us if your personal details change or are incorrect by emailing us at dataprivacy@littledayout.com.

We endeavor to ensure that your information is relevant to its intended use, accurate, and complete. You can access and update your contact information by visiting your subscriptions page on the Little Day Out Website. You can close your Little Day Out account by contacting us at the email address listed below. We will send you an e-mail to confirm your request. Please note that after you close an account, you will not be able to sign in or access any of your personal information. However, you can open a new account at any time. Please also note that we may retain certain information associated with your account in our archives, including for recordkeeping integrity.

As discussed above, you can choose not to provide us with any information, although it may be needed to take advantage of certain features offered on Little Day Out.

If you do not wish to receive marketing materials from us, please write to us at the email address below or email [hello@littledayout.com](mailto:hello@littledayout.com). Unless you tell us otherwise, we may contact you by telephone, mail, SMS and/or email.

**External Links**

If any part of the Little Day Out Website links you to other websites, those external Web sites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

As part of our efforts to ensure that we properly manage, protect and process your personal data, we will be reviewing our policies, procedures and processes from time to time. Little Day Out may change, add or delete to this Privacy Policy or any portion thereof from time to time in its sole and absolute discretion where it deems it necessary for legal, general regulatory and technical purposes, or due to changes in the services provided. Thereafter, you expressly agree to any such amended Privacy Policy. Any amended Privacy Policy will be posted on our website at www.littledayout.com.  You are encouraged to visit the website from time to time to ensure that you are well informed of our latest policies in relation to personal data protection.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have clarifications, corrections, issues, access or information requests about your data which we hold, you may wish to write to us at:

Big Little Company Pte. Ltd.  
20 Maxwell Road #09-17  
Singapore 069113  

If you wish to contact us about a Data Protection concern, please write to The Data Privacy Officer at the address shown above or email to [dataprivacy@littledayout.com](mailto:dataprivacy@littledayout.com). We will certainly strive to deal with your concern, or any complaint or grievance that you may have speedily and fairly.

_Last updated: June 2014_
